Name: Huthaifah Bahir

Address: Baghdad

Phone NO.: +9647717745214

Date of birth: 17/6/1994

Email: Huthyfa.Point@yahoo.com

Summary: -

Highly efficient and motivated administrator with great communication skills, leadership and initiative spirit, the ability to negotiate and dealing with different categories of people. capable of using Microsoft office programs (word, outlook, Excel and PowerPoint) and the accredited systems in the international humanitarian organizations. Previous experience with companies and organizations either in the technical or administrative departments. Flexibility and the ability of working in different environments.

Work History:

• Work experience:

- Tawasul organization:

I'd worked in this organization since 2017 till present, and I'm responsible for:

- 1- Managing the workshops and activities which are targeting the volunteers.
- 2- Organizing the meetings, festivals, and events which are related to the humanitarian field.
- 3- Coordinating with the local and international NGOs.
- 4- Supervising the archiving system and following up with the governmental approvals.
- 5- Managing the programs of the organization.

- Halat Alrafidien communication company:

I'd worked in this company as technician during (2016-2017) and I was responsible for:

- 1- Supervising the internet café which relates to the company.
- 2- Preparing the purchase order for the desired equipment.
- 3- Fixing any urgent jam or damage.
- 4- Monitoring the electrical system, generators, and fuel.

- Alzawraa park:

I'd worked as an accountant during the time period (2012-2016).

Alkoukh company:

I'd worked as a seller during the time period (2010-2012).

Voluntary work:

1- One thousand campaign:

I was one of the founders and a member of senior management team of the campaign during the time period (2013-2017).

2- Almaljaa team for humanitarian support and development:

I founded this team during the crises of ISIS occupation in 2016, and I was managing most of the implemented programs and activities since 2016 till present.

And I can summarize my experience and responsibilities in the voluntary work by the following points:

- 1- Communicating with the donors and planning for the projects and activities according to the available budget.
- 2- Organizing awareness sessions for the children which were coordinated with (the Iraqi red crescent associate) about health and personal hygiene in the newly liberated areas and the camps, and I worked as a hygiene promotor as well.
- 3- Affording the mental health support for children and adults in the schools, camps, and newly liberated areas.

- 4- I'd been certified by (the Iraqi red crescent associate) to work as a first aider, so I was affording the desired support in the (camps, newly liberated areas, marathons, and festivals).
- 5- Performing many sessions and workshops regarding the voluntary work, team building, and leadership.
- 6- Supervising the implemented projects and activities.

Education:-

- Year of graduation: 2016, Bachelor degree in Islamic sciences / Alimam Alathem college.

Certificates:

-

Core skills:

- Administrative support and good communication skills.
- Previous experience in human resources field.
- Preparing the formal letters and reports for the governmental and non-governmental entities.
- Following up in the governmental ministries and directorates with good knowledge of the governmental procedures and regulations.
- Auditing the content of the websites.
- Filing and data archiving.
- Negotiation and marketing skills.
- Team worker.

Languages:

- Arabic, mother tong.
- English, good fluency in speaking, reading writing and listening.